A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Administration, Building Services, Ford Foundation Headquarters, New Building Planning and Construction Files FA500
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Design and Planning, 1951-1970, bulk 1963-1968; 1963-1968; II; 5.41 Cubic Feet
  - Maintenance -- Proposals, 1964-1965 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Management -- Cross and Brown -- Proposal, 1965 March 10 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Management -- Real Estate -- William A. White and Co., 1965 February 11-April 13 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Management Contractor -- Selection -- Draft Letters to Turner and Fuller, 1963 June 20 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Medical Area -- Notes, 1963 June 28 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Movable Partition System, 1964 August 10 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Move to New Building -- Informational Literature, 1967-1968 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Move to New Building -- Proposals, 1966-1967 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Nerva-Plast -- Product Information, 1965 January 25 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Nicely, J. M. -- Property Acquisition and Zoning, 1963 February-1964 February (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Pamphlets and Brochures -- Visits to Other Buildings (1 of 2), circa 1957-1967 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Pamphlets and Brochures -- Visits to Other Buildings (2 of 2), circa 1957-1967 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Parks Department -- Access Roads and Walks -- Correspondence Re: East Stairwell Exit with Background, 1964 October 1-1965 May 10 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Parks Department -- Application -- Correspondence Re: Exit Door Easement, Permit, Pictures, Plans (See: Visual Images--Photos), 1964 October 28-1965 November 3 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Personnel and Space Analysis -- Budgeted Positions -- Data and Lists, 1964-1965 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Personnel and Space Analysis -- Economic Analysis of 320 E. 43rd Street -- Notes and Memorandum, 1965 December 8 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Personnel and Space Analysis -- Space Assignment, 1966 January 11 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Personnel and Space Analysis -- Telephone Systems -- Memoranda, Telephone Room Plans, Background, 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Photostat Drawings -- 10A, 19, 23 and Elevation -- 321 East 43rd Street Erected 1911, 1963 June 11 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Planning and Designs -- Correspondence with Brookings Institute, etc. Re: Ford Foundation New Building Plans, 1964 January 7-March 27 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Planning Requirements -- Crowe, T.J., 1964 April 16-22 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Planning Requirements (1 of 2), 1964 April 22 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Planning Requirements (2 of 2), 1964 April 22 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Plumbing -- Jarcho Brothers -- Proposed Specifications (1 of 2), 1965 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Plumbing -- Jarcho Brothers -- Proposed Specifications (2 of 2), 1965 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Program Assignments -- Obsolete -- Floor Plans, undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Property Purchase -- Plans for Hospital, Purchase of Berk Industries and Grand Central Hospital Closure, Deeds, Title Insurance, 1963 March 7-1966 April 11 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Proposals -- Bid Documents (1 of 2), 1964-1965 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Proposals -- Bid Documents (2 of 2), 1964-1965 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Prospective Contractors -- Brochures (1 of 2), 1963 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Prospective Contractors -- Brochures (2 of 2), 1963-1965 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Protection and Maintenance of Site -- Correspondence and Proposed Agreement Re: Security, Snow Removal, 1963 June 13-1965 December 20 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Real Estate Notifications -- Space for Rent Letters, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Reception Areas -- Notes Re: Design, UN Pass, 1964 November 24 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Rental Space -- 800 Second Avenue -- Sub-leases and Correspondence, 1965-1967 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Rezoning -- Notes, 1962 October 9-1963 June 7 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Roche -- Ford Foundation Headquarters -- Addenda and Bulletins (1 of 3), 1965 July (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Roche -- Ford Foundation Headquarters -- Addenda and Bulletins (2 of 3), 1965 August-December (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Roche -- Ford Foundation Headquarters -- Addenda and Bulletins (3 of 3), 1965 December-1967 April (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Roche -- Ford Foundation Headquarters Specifications, 1965 May 3 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Roll-up Doors -- Kinnear Manufacturing Co -- Correspondence Re: Specification Approval, 1967 February 21-May 29 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Roof Storage -- Memorandum Re: Cancelling Plan, 1967 February 15 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Security -- Minutes and Memoranda Re: Security Plan, 1965 November 12-1967 May 22 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Service Areas -- Notes and Memoranda, 1964 June 3 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Sewer -- Correspondence Re: Building Sewer Connection Design, 1965 April 22 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Shelter Area -- Memorandum, Correspondence and Background Re: Installing Civil Defense Area, 1964 August 25-December 10 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Shop Drawings -- Correspondence Re: Schedule, 1964 December 15-1966 October 5 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Site Development -- Planning Requirements Cover Letters, Traffic Regulations, 1963 November 5-1964 September 17 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Site Purchase -- Correspondence, Hospital Inventory, Copies of Deeds for Property and Purchase of Berk Industries, 1963 March 1-1964 February 17 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Space Assignments -- Obsolete -- Plans, Details, Comments, etc., 1967 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Space Requirements -- Memoranda and Floor Plans, 1962-1965 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Special Areas -- Memoranda and Background Re: AV Design, 1964-1965 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Staff Suggestions, 1963-1964 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Staff Suggestions -- General -- Memoranda Re: Building Committee Meeting w/Architects, 1963 August 7-1964 February 27 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Steam Supply System -- Correspondence with Consolidated Edison (Con Ed), 1965 January 26-June 4 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Storm Drainage System -- Memorandum Re: Cistern, 1966 March 10 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Storm, Sanitary Drains and Plumbing -- Requisition Request, 1965 June 28 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Structural -- Excavation and Foundations -- Inspection Report, 1964 August 26 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Structural -- "SK" Sketches, 1966-1968 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Structural System -- Correspondence and Background Re: Steel Supports, Cor-Ten, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Structural Walls -- Memoranda and Background Re: Cor-Ten Steel, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Surveys -- Correspondence Re: Surveying, Easement Survey, Plans, 1963 June 4-1968 June 18 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Surveys of Site -- Zoning Map, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Telephone System -- New York Telephone -- Proposal, Correspondence Re: Telephone Equipment Room, Plans (1 of 2), 1965-1966 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Telephone System -- New York Telephone -- Memoranda and Plans Re: Centrex Cancellation (2 of 2), 1967 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Toilet Rooms -- Correspondence and Plans Re: Design, 1963-1966 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Turner Construction Co. -- General Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Under-Surface Investigation -- Sub-surface Test Report, 1963 June 28-December 18 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Utilities and Building Operation, 1964 September 4 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Visits to and Notes Re: Other Buildings, 1963-1966 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Window Washing Equipment -- Western Gear -- Skyclimber -- Proposal and Design Stress Analysis, 1966 August 24 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Construction Files, 1959-1971, bulk 1963-1969; 1963-1969; III; 12.87 Cubic Feet
  Series III. Construction Files, 1959-1970 (bulk 1963-1969)
  This series holds files pertaining to the physical construction and assembly of the new headquarters building. Arranged in alphabetical order, the files contain meeting minutes and reports to the Trustees' Building Committee (1963-1970). Schedules, contracts, and building design meeting minutes regarding specific aspects of construction document the Turner Construction Company's operations as management contractor. Files about the design, installation and troubleshooting of the HVAC system are particularly extensive, as are reports created during the construction process. These include daily construction reports, as well as excavation reports, vibration studies, and structural steel analyses.
  - Acoustical Ceilings -- William J. Scully Acoustics Corp. -- Diagrams, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Acoustical Consultants -- Michael J. Kodaras, Inc., 1967 June 7 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Architects -- Field Memorandums, 1966 January 27-1968 January 27 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Architects -- Field Orders, 1966 February 25-1968 January 5 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Architects -- Finish Schedule, undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Architects -- Luncheons with Architect and Management Contractor -- Agenda, 1965 November 19 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Architectural Metals -- General Bronze Corp. -- Correspondence Re: Specifications, 1966 October 11-1967 October 3 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Architectural Metals -- J.W. Fiske -- Illustrations and Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Armor Elevators -- Sketches and Plans, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Audiovisual -- Rosner TV -- Cost (1 of 2), 1967 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Audiovisual -- Rosner TV -- Cost (2 of 2), 1967-1969 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Authorizations and Directives -- Memoranda, 1964 February 18-1965 March 3 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Acoustics -- Correspondence Re: Consulting, 1965 January 26 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Bidders and Quotations -- Various Trades, 1965 July (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Boring -- Haller Testing Laboratories -- Blueprints, Bidding, Contract, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Building Audit -- Price Waterhouse, 1970 March 10 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Budget -- Budget, Monthly Cost Control Report, Cost Studies (1 of 2), 1964-1966 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Budget -- Cost Studies, Accounting Procedures, Status of Orders (2 of 2), 1964-1966 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Budget -- Miscellaneous Budget Lists and Correspondence, 1963-1965 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Budget -- Monthly Control Reports, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Building Enclosure -- American Bridge -- Contract, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Building Planning Committee -- Correspondence, General Data, Minutes (1 of 2), 1963-1965 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Building Planning Committee -- Correspondence, General Data, Minutes (2 of 2), 1963-1967 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Bulletins, Agenda and Room Finish Schedules (1 of 2), 1965-1967 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Bulletins, Agenda and Room Finish Schedules (2 of 2), 1965-1967 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Ceramic Tiles -- Del Turco Brothers -- Correspondence Re: Tile Samples, 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Changes, Alterations, Additions -- Memoranda, Floor Plans, Change Orders, 1968 January 31-September 24 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Charles Kurzon Inc. -- Keying Schedule, Plans, Background, 1966-1968 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - C.I. Designs -- Correspondence Re: Billing Dispute with Invoices, 1967-1969 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Computer -- Matrix Corporation -- Specifications, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Computerized Building Construction Control Network and Bar Chart, 1966 February 23-1967 January 1 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Concrete Pours -- Daily Record, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Concrete Pours -- Sketches -- Floor Plans, circa 1966 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Concrete Quality Supervision -- Robert Hunt and Co., 1964-1968 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Contractors -- Building Construction -- Proposals and Correspondence Re: Selection, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Contracts -- Dan Kiley, Casale & Nowell, Joseph N. Lacy, John V. Dinan, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Core Borings -- Severud-Elstad-Krueger-Assoc. -- Agreement and Memoranda, 1963 June 20-1968 December 30 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Core Drilling -- Jersey Equipment and Tool, 1966 May 10 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Cosentini Associates -- Personnel Memoranda, 1959-1965 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Cost Analysis -- Budget -- Monthly Reports with Memoranda, 1964-1967 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Cost Analysis -- Building Construction Costs, 1970 March 1 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Cost Analysis -- Classification of Building Construction Costs, 1970 March 1 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Cost Analysis -- Commercial Construction Cost Basis, 1970 March 1 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Cost Analysis -- Memoranda, Notes, Spreadsheets, etc., 1966-1970 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Cost Analysis -- Miscellaneous Work Sheets, 1965-1969 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Cost Analysis -- Monthly Control Reports, 1966-1968 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Cost Analysis -- Reasons for Changes in Costs to Sub-contracts, 1970 Mach 1 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Cost Analysis -- Sub-contractors to Turner Construction Co., 1970 March 1 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Cost Breakdown -- Exhibit A, undated (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Critical Path Work Schedule -- Correspondence, Charts, Contract (1 of 2), 1965 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Critical Path Work Schedule -- Charts, Contract (2 of 2), 1965 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Demolition -- Letters to Bidders, 1963 March 6-August 7 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Demolition -- Lipsett Division -- Contract with Ford Foundation, 1963 August 6 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Detailed Analysis -- Additions to Contract Award, 1967 January 11 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Directives, 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Electrical -- J. Livingston and Co. -- Electrical Generator, Diagram, Report, etc. (1 of 5), 1965 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Electrical -- J. Livingston and Co. -- Electrical Generator, Diagram, Report, etc. (2 of 5), 1965-1968 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Electrical -- J. Livingston and Co. -- Electrical Generator, Diagram, Report, etc. (3 of 5), 1965-1968 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Electrical -- J. Livingston and Co. -- Electrical Generator, Diagram, Report, etc. (4 of 5), 1965-1968 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Electrical -- J. Livingston and Co. -- Diagram and Report (5 of 5), circa 1969 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Electrical Service (temporary) -- M. Eisenberg and Bros., 1965 February 2-5 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Excavation -- Boring Logs, 1964 September-October (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Excavations and Foundations -- Sketches and Investigation Reports, 1964 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Grading and Backfill -- Anthony Muratore Contracting Co. -- Subcontract, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Elevators -- Armor Elevators -- Button Selection, 1966 May 10 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Finish Hardware -- Charles Kurzon Inc. (1 of 2), 1965-1968 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Finish Hardware -- Charles Kurzon Inc. (2 of 2), 1965-1968 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Fire Protection -- Leeder Fire Protection Co., 1966 December 7 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Foundation -- T. Crimmins Contracting -- Minutes, Background, Sketches Re: Foundations, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Garden -- Main Garden and Plantings -- Dan Kiley -- Plans and Correspondence, 1966 October-December (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Garage -- Memoranda and Plans, 1965-1968 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Glass and Glazing Work -- Samuel Kirschner and Sons Inc., 1965-1967 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Hardware -- Charles Kurzon -- Schedules (1 of 3), 1966 February 9 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Hardware -- Charles Kurzon -- Schedules (2 of 3), 1966 April 1-October 28 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Hardware -- Charles Kurzon -- Schedules (3 of 3), 1966 December 15-1967 August 23 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Hardware -- Schedules for Movable Partitions, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Hermitage Wall Facing -- Specification, 1966 December 13 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Hoist Tower and Hoisting Equipment -- Heydt Contracting Corp., 1965-1966 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Hollow Metal Doors -- Firedoor Corp. -- Plans, 1966 May 19-1967 December 5 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Hollow Metal Work -- Doors and Frames -- Firedoor Corp. of America -- Contract and Bidding, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Housing Administration Department of Buildings -- Application and Management Agreement, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - HVAC -- Barber Colman Co. -- Equipment Lists, Schedules, etc. (1 of 3), 1966 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - HVAC -- Barber Colman Co. -- Specifications (2 of 3), 1966 July 4-August 4 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - HVAC -- Barber Colman Co. -- Mixed-box Check (3 of 3), 1968 June 24 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - HVAC -- Color Code Chart, 1965 November 16 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - HVAC -- Conference Room and Board Room, 1968 March-June (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - HVAC -- Cutler-Hammer -- Plans, 1966 January 6 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - HVAC -- Fans and Air Handlers, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - HVAC -- Havens -- Cooling Towers -- Plans, 1965 November 4-1966 May 19 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - HVAC -- Kerby Saunders -- Air Balancing Data (1 of 2), 1965 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - HVAC -- Kerby Saunders -- Air Balancing Data (2 of 2), 1967 December 16 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - HVAC -- Kerby Saunders -- Approval Drawings, 1966 June 22 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - HVAC -- Kerby Saunders -- Chromalox, 1968 February (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - HVAC -- Kerby Saunders -- General -- Thermostat Control Meeting, Costs, Problems, Billing, Minutes, Background, etc. (1 of 5), 1966-1968 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - HVAC -- Kerby Saunders -- General -- Punch Lists, etc. (2 of 5), 1965-1968 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - HVAC -- Kerby Saunders -- General -- Change Orders, Contract, Proposal, Bidding, etc. (3 of 5), 1965-1968 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - HVAC -- Kerby Saunders -- General -- Billing, Minutes (4 of 5), 1968-1970 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - HVAC -- Kerby Saunders -- General -- Minutes, Background (5 of 5), 1963-1968 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - HVAC -- Kerby Saunders -- Submittal Data (1 of 2), 1965-1966 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - HVAC -- Kerby Saunders -- Submittal Data (2 of 2), 1966 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - HVAC -- Log of Job Activities -- Minutes, 1969 January (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - HVAC -- Mechanical Systems -- Specifications and Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - HVAC -- Memoranda Re: HVAC System, 1966-1967 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - HVAC -- Minutes, Memoranda, Invoices Re: HVAC, Plumbing, etc. (1 of 4), 1965 November-1966 February (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - HVAC -- Minutes, Memoranda, Invoices Re: HVAC, Plumbing, etc. (2 of 4), 1966 March-April (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - HVAC -- Minutes, Memoranda, Invoices Re: HVAC, Plumbing, etc. (3 of 4), 1966 May-September (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - HVAC -- Minutes, Memoranda, Invoices Re: HVAC, Plumbing, etc. (4 of 4), 1966 October-1967 March (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - HVAC -- National Sheet Metal -- Plans, 1965 December 2 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - HVAC -- Notes, Drawings, etc. (1 of 2), 1965-1966 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - HVAC -- Notes, Drawings, etc. (2 of 2), 1966-1967 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - HVAC -- Temperatures in Building -- Studies on Equipment Performance, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - HVAC -- Total CFM -- Data and Plans, 1968 June 18 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - HVAC -- Trane, 1968 February (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Iron Work -- Grossman Steel Stair Corp. -- Change Orders, Correspondence Re: Price, etc., 1965-1968 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - John Swenson Granite Co. -- Approval of Materials, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - John V. Dinan Consulting Engineers -- Brochure, 1966 April 16 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Kitchen Equipment -- Straus Duparquet -- Book of Illustrations, 1966 June 9 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Kitchen Equipment -- Straus Duparquet -- Correspondence Re: Equipment Purchases, Third Party Litigation; Minutes, Contract, Change Orders, etc. (1 of 3), 1966-1968 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Kitchen Equipment -- Straus Duparquet -- Correspondence Re: Equipment Purchases, Third Party Litigation; Minutes, Contract, Change Orders, etc. (2 of 3), 1968 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Kitchen Equipment -- Straus Duparquet -- Correspondence Re: Equipment Purchases, Third Party Litigation; Minutes, Contract, Change Orders, etc. (3 of 3), 1968-1971 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Lighting -- Correspondence, Memoranda, Notes Re: Office and Street Lighting, 1964-1968 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Lipsett Division, Luria Bros. and Co., Inc. -- Contract with Ford Foundation, 1963 December 26 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Mail Conveyor -- Lamson Corp., 1965 September 8 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Management Committee Meeting -- Minutes, 1966-1968 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Management Contractor -- Procedures, 1964 April 16-1966 February 28 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Masonry -- John B. Kelly Inc., 1966-1968 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Mechanical and Electrical -- Cosentini Associates -- Correspondence and Proposal Re: HVAC, etc., 1963 August 23-1969 February 27 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Millwork and Carpentry -- Irving and Casson -- A.H. Davenport Co., 1967 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Mineral Tile Ceilings -- William J. Scully Acoustics Corp. -- Correspondence, Notes, Contracts, 1966 March 29-1968 August 15 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Mirrors and Miscellaneous Glass -- Haber and Henry Inc., 1967 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Movable Metal Partitions and Wall Liner -- Mills Company -- Change Orders, Contract, Bidding, Correspondence Re: Production Problems, Claims, Analysis (1 of 4), 1966-1969 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Movable Metal Partitions and Wall Liner -- Mills Company -- Change Orders, Contract, Bidding, Correspondence Re: Production Problems, Claims, Analysis (2 of 4), 1966-1967 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Movable Metal Partitions and Wall Liner -- Mills Company -- Change Orders, Contract, Bidding, Correspondence Re: Production Problems, Claims, Analysis (3 of 4), 1967-1969 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Movable Metal Partitions and Wall Liner -- Mills Company -- Change Orders, Contract, Bidding, Correspondence Re: Production Problems, Claims, Analysis (4 of 4), 1967-1968 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - New York City Building Codes -- Approved Amendments, Drawings, etc., 1967 March 29 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Operating and Maintenance -- Keying Schedule, 1965-1966 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Ornamental Iron Work -- J.W. Fiske Architectural Metals -- Contract, Bidding, Change Orders, 1965-1968 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Painting, Miscellaneous Corrective -- Stuart-Dean Co., Inc. -- Contracts, 1967 June 21-1968 May 22 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Painting Work -- J.I. Hass Co. Inc. -- Contracts, 1967-1968 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Personnel -- Listing of Ford Foundation Officials and Organizational Chart, 1963 November (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Photographs -- Mal Gurian Associates -- Contract, Insurance, Correspondence, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Piping -- Underground Piping "As Is" -- Drawings, 1968 March 28 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Planting Work -- Everett Conklin and Co., Inc. -- Correspondence and Notes Re: Estimate and Plant List (1 of 4), 1964-1965 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Planting Work -- Everett Conklin and Co. -- Interim Reports and Quotations, etc. (2 of 4), 1965-1966 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Planting Work -- Everett Conklin and Co. -- Contract, Correspondence Re: Quotes, Plant Types, etc. (3 of 4), 1965-1969 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Planting Work -- Everett Conklin and Co. -- Contract and Bidding (4 of 4), 1966-1968 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Planting Work -- Permit for Tree Planting, 1967 May 15 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Plumbing -- Jarcho Bros., Inc. -- Contract, Change Orders (1 of 3), 1965-1968 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Plumbing -- Jarcho Bros., Inc. -- Change Orders, Directives, Work Authorization (2 of 3), 1965-1968 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Plumbing -- Jarcho Bros., Inc. -- Bid, Proposal, Change Order (3 of 3), 1965-1967 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Plumbing System -- Correspondence Re: Directive and List, 1964 October 5-1966 March 30 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Primary Power -- Consolidated Edison (Con Ed) -- Correspondence, Memoranda and Diagrams Re: Electric and Gas Supply, 1964-1967 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Procedures -- Correspondence and Memoranda, 1963 September 17-1966 February 28 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Procedures and Approvals, 1964 April 15-1965 April 20 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Punch List, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Reinforcing Steel Detailing -- Invoices, 1965 August 10-1966 February 7 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Reports -- Areas Examined -- Park West and South Retaining Walls -- John V. Dinan Consulting Engineers, 1964 March 20 (Box 28, Folder 10)